americanantiagingspotlight.com 2009-03-01

# American Anti-Aging Association - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com respects privacy of Internet Users and does not collect personally identifying information without the Internet User's permission.

**Collection of Data**

AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com does not collect Internet User identity or contact information from Internet Users' visits to AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com Web Sites. For each visitor to a AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com Web site, the visitor's computer reaches us via a particular IP, (Internet Protocol), address. AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com's servers automatically collect this IP address.

An Internet User's browser sets Cookies (when enabled) that contain small amounts of data on the Internet User's computer after a visit to any web site. Cookies assist AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com in tracking Internet Users' activities beginning from a Publisher's web site or subscription e-mail through an Advertiser's web site that the Internet User links to from the Publisher's site or e-mail. If the Internet User re-visits the Advertiser's site directly, AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com is able to continue to track the Internet User's activities on the Advertiser's site and reward the Publisher that referred the Internet User. The Cookies themselves tell AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com nothing about the Internet User personally.

No information is obtained from the Internet User or Internet User's computer to generate the unique identifying number of the Internet User. AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com's servers automatically generate the unique number. None of AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com's Cookies are used to perform "User Profiling".

AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com does receive and record partial e-mail addresses of Internet Users, only in circumstances where the Internet User has voluntarily provided its identity and contact information through the Advertiser's Web site or Publisher's Web site. This partial e-mail address does not enable AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com to personally identify an Internet User.

**Use and Disclosure of Data**

AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com does not sell or rent personally identifying information. AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com does not disclose personally identifying information to anyone that AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com is not authorized to do so. AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com uses anonymous user data to create and report the browsing, purchasing and/or lead form completion activities of anonymous users.

AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com reserves the right to release information on Internet Users if compelled to do so by proper judicial or governmental authorities. Disclosure shall be limited to only to those that AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com is compelled to disclose to. At present, all information processing occurs in the United States.

**Security Measures**

AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com employs industry standard security measures to ensure the security of all data. Access to AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com customer data is accessible via password protection through the Advertiser and Publisher Accounts created by each Advertiser and Publisher, and to designated AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com employees who require system level access in order to perform their jobs. Access to Internet User data that identifies the Internet User's name and/or e-mail addresses is limited to designated AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com employees who require such access in order to perform their jobs and to an Advertiser or Publisher that provided such information. Each Advertiser and Publisher is responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of its own password used for accessing its accounts on the AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com Network.

**Subscription E-mails**

AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com is a direct marketer that delivers email messages to its subscribers. When working with its merchants, AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com reserves the right to review and edit outgoing messages to ensure messages are delivered to subscribers. All information voluntarily provided to AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com by a registrant may be used to support our marketing partner's data services business. These services include the provision of personally identifiable data to marketing companies, advertising agencies, data compilers, data companies, and, to the extent permitted by law, individual reference, email marketers and look-up service programs. Such information may be used by such companies to provide users via email with information on products and services that may be of interest to them. Users may unsubscribe to electronic mailings sent by us at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of every AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com newsletter or mailing.

**COPPA**

Since you may not become a member of AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com's Network if you are under the age of 18, AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. Advertisers and Publishers are also obligated to comply with COPPA.

If you inform AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com that AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com has collected or received information from a child under 18, AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com will delete such information immediately from its databases. No AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com Web Site is specifically directed to children under 18. AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com shall not knowingly distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information erroneously collected from children under 18.

**Deactivating or deleting from databases by Publishers and Advertisers**

Please contact us if you no longer wish to maintain an account with AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com, or are unable to access your account. If AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com has such information, AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com shall not retain your name and/or e-mail address any longer than is necessary to perform the services that you requested from AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com. To contact AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com, contact us at info@AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com.

**Policy Changes**

AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com may find it necessary or be legally obligated to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any changes will be posted at this site. Except as otherwise required by law, modifications to this Privacy Policy will not affect the privacy of data collected by AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com prior to the effective date of the policy change.

Effective Dec. 17, 2007 

Copyright © 2008 AmericanAntiAgingAssociation.com All Rights Reserved
